<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="card_picture_1" >
        <item>@drawable/music</item>
    </string-array>
    <integer-array name="Arti_imgs">
        <item>@drawable/image_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_3</item>
        <item>@drawable/image_4</item>
    </integer-array>
    <string-array name="music_track_1">
    <item >Sound</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Artifacts">
        <item>Sarnath is a city located 13 kilometres north-east of Varanasi near the confluence of the Ganges and the Varuna rivers in Uttar Pradesh, India. The deer park in Sarnath is where Gautama Buddha first taught the Dharma, and where the Buddhist Sangha came into existence through the enlightenment of Kondanna. Singhpur, a village approximately one km away from the site, was the birthplace of Shreyansanath, the Eleventh Tirthankara of Jainism, and a temple dedicated to him, is an important pilgrimage site.
        </item>
        <item>The Veena,also spelled as Vina or Been or Bina, is a multistringed chordophone of the Indian subcontinent.It is an ancient musical instrument that evolved into many variations, such as lutes, zithers and arched harps.The many regional designs have different names such as the Rudra veena, the Saraswati veena, the Mohan veena and others</item>

        <item>A Banarasi saree is a saree made in Varanasi, a city which is also called Benares or Banaras. The sarees are among the finest sarees in India and are known for their gold and silver brocade or zari, fine silk and opulent embroidery. The sarees are made of finely woven silk and are decorated with intricate design, and, because of these engravings, are relatively heavy.

Their special characteristics are Mughal inspired designs such as intricate intertwining floral and foliate motifs, kalga and bel, a string of upright leaves called jhallar at the outer, edge of border is a characteristic of these sarees. Other features are gold work, compact weaving, figures with small details, metallic visual effects, pallus, jal, and mina work</item>

        <item>Moradabad is a city, commissionary, and a municipal corporation in Moradabad district, Uttar Pradesh. It was established in 1625A.D. by Rustam Khan and is named after prince Murad Baksh, the son of the Mughal Emperor Shah Jahan.

Moradabad is situated on the banks of the Ramganga river, at a distance of 167 km from the national capital, New Delhi and 344 km north-west of the state capital Lucknow. The city is known as Pital Nagri, for its famous brass handicrafts industry.It is also the divisional headquarters of Northern Railway</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>